声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：skier_airman校对：扣扣
后期：阿胜 双语制作：冰小赐  雯雯  七色九天
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
天哪
Oh, my God!
Walt! Walt!
离机油远点儿  在那别动
Stay away from the gas! Stay there!
救命  救命
Help! Help!
救命啊
Somebody, help me!
救命  救命
Help, help!
我的腿
Oh, my leg!
过来  帮我一下
Hey, get over here. Give me a hand.
You, come on! Come over here! Give me a hand!
数三下一起用力
On the count of three.
一 二 三
One, two, three!
救命  救救我
Help me! Please, help me!
把他抬走  离引擎远点儿
Get him out of here. Get him away from the engine.
把他抬走
Get him out of here.
救救我! 请救救我! 我开始宫缩了
Help me! Please, help me. I'm having contractions!
怀孕几个月了
How many months pregnant are you?
八个月
Only eight months.
间隔时间呢
How far apart are they coming?
不知道  这是头一次
I don't know, a few just happened!
快躲开
Hey! Get away from there!
听我说
Listen to me!
看着我  你会没事的  知道吗
Look at me! You're gonna be okay. Do you understand me?
但你必须坐着别动
But you have to sit absolutely still.
你  过来
Hey! You! Come here!
让她离这些烟远点儿
I need you to get this woman away from these fumes.
带她到那边去  陪着她
Take her there. Stay with her.
如果宫缩频率接近三分钟就叫我
If her contractions occur closer than three minutes, call me!
不是吧
You gotta be kidding me.
我马上就回来  好吗
I'll be right back.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你叫什么名字啊
Hey! What's your name?
Jack!
停 她头部后仰不够  气都送到了她胃里
Stop! Her head's not tilted back enough. You're blowing into her stomach.
你肯定吗
You sure?
我刚才就是这么做的啊
That's exactly what I was doing.
我是救生员  有执照的
I'm a lifeguard. I'm licensed.
你该考虑一下把那执照还回去了
You need to think about giving that license back.
也许我们该试一下插孔
Maybe we should do one of those hole things.
用钢笔在喉部插孔
Stick the pen in the throat?
好主意呀  你给我找个钢笔去
Yeah, good idea. You go get me a pen.
谁有钢笔  有钢笔吗
Does anyone have any pens? Do you have a pen?
醒过来  醒过来
Come on! Come on!
深呼吸
Big deep breaths.
Big breaths.
离开那儿  离开那儿
Move! Move! Move!
带她离开  带她离开那儿  走开啊!
Get her up! Get her out of there! Go away!
没事吧
You okay?
恩
Yeah. Yeah.
你呢
You?
陪着她
Stay with her.
老兄  这还用说
Dude, I'm not going anywhere.
不知道哪个最好用
I didn't know which one would work best.
都不错
They're all OK.
谢了
Thanks.
不好意思
Excuse me.
你用过针吗
Did you ever use a needle?
什么
What?
你缝过牛仔裤吗
Did you ever patch a pair of jeans?
我...
I, uh...
我在家做过窗帘
I made the drapes in my apartment.
好极了  听我说
That's fantastic. Listen...
有时间能帮我个忙吗
Do you have a second? I could use a little help here.
什么忙
Help with what?
这个
With this.
我是一名医生 本可以自己来的  可够不到...
I'd do it myself, I'm a doctor, but I just can't reach it.
你想让我缝那伤口吗
You want me to sew that?
就像是缝窗帘一样
Like the drapes.
不  我是用缝纫机缝的窗帘
No, I used a sewing machine.
不  你行的  真的
No, you can do this, I'm telling you.
如果你不介意的话
If you wouldn't mind.
当然可以
Of course I will.
多谢了
Thank you.
给你的手消毒
It's for your hand.
给我留些  给伤口消毒
Save me some... for there...for the wound.
对颜色有要求吗
Any color preference?
没有  标准黑颜色
No. Standard black.
嘿  你
Hey, you!
叫什么名字
What's your name?
我吗  Charlie
Me? Charlie.
Charlie 帮忙生火  火光不够大就没人会发现我们
Charlie, we need help with the fire. No one will see it if it isn't big.
好  交给我吧
Okay, I'm on it.
你的名字呢
What's your name?
Sayid.
交给我吧  Sayid
Sayid. I'm on it, Sayid.
我可能会吐你一身
I might throw up on you.
你干的不错
You're doing fine.
你看起来一点儿也不害怕
You don't seem afraid at all.
我不明白
I don't understand that.
恐惧算是一件怪异的事
Well, fear's sort of an odd thing.
在我实习的时候
When I was in residency,
我第一次主刀是为一名16岁孩子作脊柱手术
my first solo procedure was a spinal surgery on a 16-year-old kid.
一个女孩子
A girl.
在13个小时以后  临近结束的时候  在我缝合的时候
And at the end, after 13 hours, I was closing her up and I...
我不小心撕开了她的硬膜腔
I accidentally ripped her dural sack.
神经集中的脊柱基部被弄碎了
It's at the base of the spine where all the nerves come together.
隔膜  隔膜组织
Membrane as thin as tissue, and...
都被撕开了
So it ripped open.
神经像细意大利面一样散出
Nerves just spilled out of her like angel hair pasta,
脊髓液流了出来
spinal fluid flowing out of her and I...
感觉如此恐怖...真实  可我知道我必须去面对
The terror was just so...crazy, so real...and I knew I had to deal with it.
于是我做出了一个选择
So I just made a choice.
我让恐惧侵袭我全身  让它令我惊慌失措
I'd let the fear in. Let it take over. Let it do its thing.
但我只给它五秒钟  就这么多
But only for five seconds, that's all I was gonna give it.
然后我开始记数
So I started to count.
一  二  三  四  五
One, two, three, four, five.
然后恐惧感消失了
And it was gone.
我重返工作  缝好了她  她没事了
I went back to work, sewed her up and she was fine.
换作是我的话  我早就夺门而出了
If that had been me, I think I would've run for the door.
我看不会
No, I don't think that's true.
你现在并没跑掉啊
You're not running now.
宿命
你以为他们现在就该到了
You think they would have come by now.
什么  谁呀
Hmm? Who?
任何人
Anyone.
真以为我会吃巧克力吗
As if I'm gonna start eating chocolate.
Shannon  我们可能要留在这一段时间了
Shannon, we may be here for a while.
飞机有黑匣子  白痴
The plane had a black box, idiot.
他们知道我们在哪儿  他们会来的
They know exactly where we are, they're coming.
我会在救生艇上吃
I'll eat on the rescue boat.
饿吗
Hungry?
恩  谢谢
Yeah. Thanks.
身体还有情况吗
Any more...you know, baby stuff?
没有了  没事了
No... I'm okay.
挺住
Well, hang in there.
恩  你也是
Yeah, you too.
够暖了吗
You sure you're warm enough?
你不能走出我的视线
我走到哪儿都要跟着我
知道吗
别理会他人  我们要呆在一起
他能活吗
Do you think he's gonna live?
你认识他吗
Do you know him?
他坐我边上
He was sitting next to me.
事发当时我们一定在四万英尺高空
We must've been at about 40,000 feet when it happened.
撞到了一个气阱  然后下落了大概...二百英尺
We hit an air pocket and dropped...maybe 200 feet.
紊流...
The turbulence was...
我昏了过去
I blacked out.
我没有
I didn't.
我看到了事发经过
I saw the whole thing.
我知道机尾没了  可我...就是没有勇气向后看
I knew that the tail was gone, but I...couldn't bring myself to look back.
然后...飞机前端脱落
And then the front end of the plane broke off.
却没落在沙滩这里
Well, it's not here on the beach.
尾部也没有
Neither is the tail.
我们要查明从哪个方向坠地的
We need to figure out which way we came in.
为什么
Why?
因为那样就有机会找到驾驶舱
There's a chance we find the cockpit.
如果它完好无损  就有可能找到无线电收发机
If it's intact, we might be able to find the transceiver.
然后我们就能发射信号  协助救援队找到我们
We could send out a signal, help the rescue party find us.
你怎么知道的这么多
How do you know all that?
上过几堂飞行课
I took a couple of flying lessons.
不是自愿的
Wasn't for me.
我看到了一些烟雾  在山谷那边
I saw some smoke...just through the valley.
如果你想去找那驾驶舱  我要和你一起去
If you're thinking about going for the cockpit, I'm going with you.
我还不知道你的名字
I don't know your name.
我叫Kate
I'm Kate.
我是Jack
Jack.
什么东西
What was that?
奇怪啊
That was weird, right?
是Vincent吗
Is that Vincent?
不是Vincent
It's not Vincent.
看见了吗
Did anybody see that?
恩
Yeah.
Boone!
可怕极了
Terrific.
酒怎么样
So, how's the drink?
不错
It's good.
反应不强烈呀
That wasn't a very strong reaction.
度数不够高
Well, it's not a very strong drink.
不要告诉别人
Just don't tell anyone.
这显然有违联邦航空局的重要规章吧
This, of course, breaks some critical FAA regulations.
借过
Excuse me.
先生  等等
Sir, excuse me!
看来他真是憋不住了
Guess he really had to go.
先生  等等
Sir, excuse me!
女士们  先生们
Ladies and gentlment
机长已经打开了"安全带"指示灯
The pilot has switched on the "fasten seatbelts" sign.
请返回您的座位并系好安全带
Please return to your seats and fasten your seatbelts.
正常情况
It's normal.
我知道  只是我坐飞机就没好受过
Oh, I know. I've just never been a very good flier.
我老公一直提醒我说飞机想上高空
My husband keeps reminding me that planes want to be in the air.
听起来他很有见地啊
Well, he sounds like a very smart man.
等他从洗手间回来后  我会把这话转告给他的
Be sure and tell him that when he gets back from the bathroom.
他回来前我会陪你
Well, I'll keep you company until he does.
别担心  会过去的
Don't worry. It's gonna be over...
听起来像是动物
It didn't sound like an animal, not exactly.
那声音总是让我觉得似曾相识
I keep thinking there was something familiar about it.
你从哪来的
Where you from?
布朗克斯
Bronx.
也许是猴子
Monkeys.
对  这里是猴岛
Monkey Island. Don't know if we're on an island...
准备好了吗
You ready?
凯特  告诉我烟从哪来  我自己去
You showed me where the smoke was. I can get there myself.
我要去
I'm coming.
那你可要换双好鞋
Well, you're gonna need better shoes.
无论那是什么  都不是自然界的
Whatever it was, it wasn't natural.
谁有防晒霜吗
Does anyone have any sunblock?
恩  我这有
Yes I do.
我刚看了机舱里面
So I was just looking inside the fuselage.
挺可怕的
It's pretty grim in there.
我们是否该对那些...尸体采取点措施呢
You think we should do something about the...B-O-D-Y-S?
你说什么那  哥们儿  尸体吗
What are you spelling, man, "bodies"?
尸体
B-O-D-I-E-S.
好主意
That sounds like a good idea.
不  他们来了以后会处理的
No, they'll deal with it when they get here.
我要去找驾驶舱了
I'm gonna go out and look for the cockpit.
看是否能找到无线电收发机  发射求救信号
See if we can find a transceiver to send a distress signal.
协助救援队
Help the rescue team.
你要照料一下伤员
You need to keep an eye on the wounded.
如果穿西装的人醒了 叫他冷静
If the guy in the suit wakes up, keep him calm,
不要让他拔出那碎片  知道吗
but don't let him remove that shrapnel. Understand?
恩  好的
Got it.
那腿部受伤的那个人呢  止血带呢
What about the guy with the leg? The tourniquet...?
止住血了  昨晚取下来了
I stopped the bleeding. I took it off last night.
他应该没事了
He should be all right.
恩  没问题  干的好
Yeah, cool. Good job.
我也去帮帮忙
I'll come with. I wanna help.
不  不需要帮忙了
I don't need any more help.
不  没关系  我不喜欢无所事事
No, it's cool. I don't really feel like standing still, so...
好极了
Excellent.
能问你些事吗
Can I ask you something?
问我吗  荣幸至致  一直等着呢
Me? I'd be thrilled. I've been waiting.
我们见过面吗
Have we ever met anywhere?
没有  不太可能
No. That would be unlikely.
可看起来面熟  是吧
I look familiar though, right?
恩
Yeah.
对不上号了吧
You can't quite place it?
恩  对不上
No, I can't.
恩  我知道了
Yeah, I think I know.
是吗
You do?
没听过这首歌吗
Never heard that song?
听过  就是不知道
I've heard it. I don't know what that...
我们唱的啊  "驱动轴 "
That's us! Drive Shaft!
看这戒指
The ring.
在芬兰的第二场巡演
Second tour of Finland.
你没听说过"驱动轴 "吗
Never heard of Drive Shaft?
那支乐队吗
The band?
是啊  乐队
Yeah, the band.
你曾经在"驱动轴"乐队
You were in Drive Shaft?
现在还在  我是贝斯手
I am in Drive Shaft. I play bass.
是啊  Charlie
Yeah. Charlie.
第三首歌  我是和音
Track three. I do backing vocals.
我朋友Beth会疯掉的  她爱死你们了
My friend Beth would freak. She loves you guys.
把Beth电话号码给我  我很乐意电话她
Give me Beth's number, I'll call. I'd love to.
你听说过"驱动轴"吗
You ever heard of Drive Shaft?
我们得继续走了
We gotta keep moving.
他们以前很不错
They were good.
他们现在也很不错  还没解散呢
They are good. Still together.
即将复出
We're in the middle of a comeback.
伙计们  这算是正常吗
You guys, is this normal?
白天变成了黑夜
Kind of day turning into night,
世界末日一样的天气
You know, end of the world-type weather.
伙计们
Is this...Guys?
你可不想去那里面  太多尸体了
I'm telling you, you don't wanna go in there! There's too many bodies!
又来了
There it is again.
天哪
Oh, my God.
我们走吧
Well, let's do this.
我们来拿无线电...
Let's get this trans...
无线电收发机
Transceiver.
无线电收发机  然后就离开
Transceiver thing and get out of here.
开门  开门
Come on!
没事吧
You okay?
恩  你呢
Yeah, you?
没事
Yeah.
我没事  Charlie没事  顺便说一句  我没事
I'm fine. Charlie's fine, by the way. I'm okay.
你不用上来
Hey, you don't have to come up here.
不  没关系
No, I'm good.
无线电收发机是什么样子
So, what does a transceiver look like?
结构复杂的对讲机
Like a complicated walkie-talkie.
听到我说话了吗
Hey, can you hear me?
把水拿来
I need that water.
给
Here. Here you go.
多少生还者
How many survived?
至少48人
At least 48.
身上有骨折吗
Does anything feel broken?
不  就是我的头...有点晕  仅此而已
No, no. Just my head's a little dizzy, that's all.
可能是脑震荡
It's probably a concussion.
已经过了多久了
How long has it been?
16个小时
Sixteen hours.
16个?
Sixteen?
有人来了吗
Has anybody come?
还没有
Not yet.
起飞六小时后  我们的无线电失灵了
Six hours in...our radio went out.
没人看得见我们
No one could see us.
我们掉头去斐济降落
We turned back to land in Fiji.
但遇到了紊流  偏离了航线一千英里
By the time we hit turbulence...we were a thousand miles off course.
他们搜救我们找错地方了
They're looking for us in the wrong place.
这里有无线电收发机
We have a transceiver.
好  这正是我们所希望的
Good, good. We were hoping.
你最好别动
You shouldn't move.
不  我没事
No, no. I'm okay.
无线电收发机就在哪里
Transceiver's right there.
就在那里
It's right there.
Charlie在哪儿
Where's Charlie?
不好用了
It's not working.
Charlie?
你在洗手间里做什么
What were you doing in the bathroom?
什么
What?
是什么鬼东西
What the hell was that?
Kate.
就在外面
It's right outside.
什么  什么在外面
What? What's right out...?
刚才发生了什么事
What the hell just happened?
Jack  快
Jack, come on!
别去管它了
Just leave it!
快跑
Okay, run!
Jack!
一
One.
二
Two.
五
Five.
Jack人呢
Where's Jack?
不知道
I don't know.
恩  他拉我起来的
He pulled me up.
他人呢
Where is he?
你怎么会不知道
How can you not know?
我们分开了
We got separated!
我跌倒了
I fell down.
他回来拉我  那东西
He came back. That thing was...
你看到了
Did you see it?
没有  可它就在那里
No. No. But it was right there.
我都快没命了  然后Jack回来拉起了我
We were dead... I was. And then Jack came back and he pulled me up.
我不知道他去哪了
I don't know where he is.
我们要回去找他
We have to go back for him.
回去吗  去那里吗
Go back? There?
Kate  那东西可是巨无霸啊
There's a certain gargantuan quality about this thing.
那就别来
Then don't come.
Kate.
我听见你喊了
I heard you shout.
听见你喊"Jack"了
I heard you shout "Jack."
顺便说一句  我叫Charlie
I'm Charlie, by the way.
什么东西
What is that?
什么...
What is...?
看到那东西了吗
Did you see it?
没有  就在我后面来着  我扑进了灌木丛中
No. It was right behind me, but I dove into the bushes.
伙计们  这是怎么搞的
Guys...how does something like that happen?
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====